{
    "id": "be96fd079b2d4804b588a3d6700ac37f",
    "title": "Word formation: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "60c6bc74faf5484599302fa3e999f07e",
            "title": "Word Formation Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We have known each other since our ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "childhood",
                        "childlike",
                        "childish"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "His hard work ……………………. him to pass his examination.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "able",
                        "enable",
                        "abled",
                        "enabled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "The manager asked the board members to ………………….. his earlier proposal.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "reconsider",
                        "consideration",
                        "considerable"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Only a fool will …………………… his net worth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "estimate",
                        "underestimate"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is a stupid and often talks ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "sense",
                        "sensible",
                        "nonsense"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Government of China has ………………….. its currency.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "valued",
                        "valuable",
                        "devalued"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Parents should not ………………… their children’s mistakes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "look",
                        "look over",
                        "overlook"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was absent because he was …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "unwell",
                        "wellness"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The judgment ……………………. in our favor.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "go",
                        "went",
                        "gone"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The judge ordered that the accused be ……………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "behead",
                        "beheading",
                        "beheaded"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The minister wants to …………………….. the capital.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "beauty",
                        "beautify",
                        "beautiful"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}